Well then you get ten percent
On your 110 kr
As they are now worth
And when you pull it out in the long term that is then
One sees the major effects of interest-on-interest effect
Overtime
So they will increase in value because you always get
Interest on your already rated money
It is an interest-on-interest effect
Very briefly explained
And now you come
The greater this interest rate on the interest rate effect
Therefore, it is extremely important that you who are young
That you are investing
As early as possible
For the greater, interest on the interest effect is.
That is what makes some get a head start against others
For example, many parents who invest their money for their children before they are even born
Which means this interest-on-interest effect can only work for the money, just over time
How to think when investing your money if you want to get an interest rate on interest effect?
Yes, I'm thinking like this
Money that I don't need